CALEB LABARDA: All right.
What is a 720, you might ask?
There's 2 types of 720s: there's a cheat 720 and a regular 720, okay?
A cheat 720 is where you jump off one foot and you do about 1 1/2 rotations, over a little bit 1 1/2 into a kick, okay?
So one jump, 1 1/2 rotation, then to a kick, and then go all the way around into a punch.
And then a regular 720 is you jump two rotations in the air, and you're going to through a hook kick out of it or a crescent kick, okay?
So a regular 720 is off both legs and a cheat 720 is off one leg.
All right.
So now a 720 was invented by a martial artist for a competition and just--it's a really showy kick, but it can be also be very powerful.
You can also hit a target or hit an opponent with it and it can be a knockout kick or a very forceful kick.
That's what a 720 would be.
It is very hard to actually hit a target but it'll take a lot of practice and a lot of timing.
But once you get it, you can actually have a lot of power coming out of a 720, and it's a really cool kick that you'd use in performances and shows.